Urban Borderlands Records MS083
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Fall 2003, MS083.003; 1.75 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Betty Stone Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Maria D. Escobar Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Jaime Vargas Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Diego F. Lopez Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Faustino DeLacruz Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Ralph G. Hergert Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Ralph G. Hergert Interview Transcript, 2003; MS083.003.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Reflections on Project by Lerome Lesser, 2003; MS083.003.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - English Language Acquisition: The Opportunities and Experience of Somerville Latino Community Final project by Lerome Lesser, Fall, 2003; MS083.003.002.00012; Lesser, Lerome (Box 2)
  - Roberto Velasquez Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Lucas A. Santos Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Joel Velasquez Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Amilcar Lopez Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Marcos Garcia Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Marcos Garcia Interview Transcription, 2003; MS083.003.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Indoor Soccer League Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Public Parks Interview Report, 2003; MS083.003.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - For the love of the Game: Latino Soccer Leagues in Somerville, Massachusetts. Final project by Joel Cohen, Fall, 2003; MS083.003.002.00021; Cohen, Joel (Box 2)
  - Esther Flores, 2003-10-01; MS083.003.003.00001 (Box 3)
    Interviewed by David Pistrang
  - Jenny Gomez, 2003-10-27; MS083.003.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Nora Garniza, 2003-10-16; MS083.003.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Luis Serrano, 2003-10-10; MS083.003.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Leo Zuniga, 2003-10-22; MS083.003.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Milagro Garcia, 2003-10-17; MS083.003.003.00006 (Box 3)
    Interviewed by Emily Chasan
  - Yony Orantes, 2003-10-13; MS083.003.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Amilcar Lopez, 2003-10-10; MS083.003.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Maria "Maryom" Grasso, 2003-10-23; MS083.003.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Ana Bran, 2003-11-03; MS083.003.003.00010 (Box 3)
    Interviewed by Emily Chasan, Bianca Salazar and Nelson Salazar
  - Ruben Salinas Stern and David Pistrang, 2003; MS083.003.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Maria Tejada, 2003-10-05; MS083.003.003.00012 (Box 3)
    Interviewed by Nora Martin-Cooley
  - Emma Ramos, 2003-10-10; MS083.003.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Alma Mejia, 2003-10-10; MS083.003.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Nelson Salazar, 2003-10-17; MS083.003.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Anonymous, 2003-10-24; MS083.003.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Rosemarie Federico and John Federico, 2003-10-24; MS083.003.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Marcos Garcia, 2003-10-31; MS083.003.003.00018 (Box 3)
    Interviewed by Cecilia Dos Santos and Lexie McGovern in spanish
  - Alma Mejia, 2003-10-29; MS083.003.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Interviewed by Cecilia Dos Santos and Lexie McGovern
  - Luis Martinez, 2003-10-16; MS083.003.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Roberto Flores, 2003-10-11; MS083.003.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Emma Ramos, 2003-10-04; MS083.003.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Ester Umanzar, 2003-11-10; MS083.003.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Ana Hilsa Flores, 2003-10-25; MS083.003.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Ana Velasquez, 2003-10-19; MS083.003.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Alma Mejia, 2003-10-05; MS083.003.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Flores, 2003-10-05; MS083.003.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Maria D. Escobar, 2003-10-04; MS083.003.004.00010 (Box 4)
    Interviewed by Lerone Lessner in spanish
  - Betty Stone, 2003-10-14; MS083.003.004.00011 (Box 4)
    Interviewed by Lerone Lessner
  - Rosa Medrano, 2003-10-15; MS083.003.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Antoniette Basualdo, 2003-10-21; MS083.003.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Edith Sanchez, 2003-10-24; MS083.003.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Ralph Hergert, 2003-11-13; MS083.003.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - F. Delacruz, 2003-11-21; MS083.003.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Diego Lopez, 2003-11-22; MS083.003.004.00017 (Box 4)
    Interviewed by Lerone Lessner in Spanish
  - Jaime Vargas, 2003-11-25; MS083.003.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Amilcar Lopez, 2003-11-07; MS083.003.005.00001 (Box 5)
    Interviewed by Joel Cohen
  - Robert Velasquez, 2003-10-01; MS083.003.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Lucas Santos, 2003-10-12; MS083.003.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Marcos Garcia, 2003-10-17; MS083.003.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Jose Velasquez, 2003-11-16; MS083.003.005.00005 (Box 5)
- Fall 2004, MS083.004; 2.0 Linear Feet; 8 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials from the Fall 2004 semester.
  - Legal Release Forms - Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Spencer Hickok, 2004; MS083.004.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Lindsey Nicholson, 2004; MS083.004.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Adrienne vanNieuwenhuizen, 2004; MS083.004.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Legal Release Forms - Julia Goldberg, Leah Rogers, 2004; MS083.004.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, 2004; MS083.004.001.00010; Chaskel, Sebastian (Box 1)
    Final project report by Sebastian Chaskel
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Manuel Perez. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Padre Omar Calix.Transcript. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Daniel Mendoza. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Patrona Perez. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Candelario Flores. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Oscar Mendoza. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Daisy Gomez. Interview Report. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - From Yucuaiquin to Somerville, Supporting Material. Photos. Sebastian Chaskel, 2004; MS083.004.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Final Report. Supporting Material. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00019; Palchik, Dalia (Box 1)
    Final project report by Dalia Palchik.
    - Concerns of Latino Business Community, 2004; MS083.004.001.00019.00001; Palchik, Dalia (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Miry Lopez, Transcript. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Ismael Orlando Tejada. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. William Fajardo. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Juan Pablo Hernandez. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Rafael Sorto. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Luis "Tony" Morales. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Rene Rosas, Teresa Ramirez. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Denise Provost. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Concerns of Latino Business Community. Nelson Salazar. Interview Report. Dalia Palchik, 2004; MS083.004.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Pastor Colixto Lopez. Interview Report. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Daisy Gomez. Interview Report. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Luis A. Morales. Transcript. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Roberto Velasquez Sr. Interview Report. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Jose L. Giron. Interview Report. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Religion and Community Among Somerville Latinos. Douglas Escabir and Juan Tejada. Interview Report. Spencer Hickok., 2004; MS083.004.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Melissa McWhinney. Transcript. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Hermeregildo Moran and Gladys Bena Yides. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Michael Gorman. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Marcos Garcia. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Ives Rose Saint-Dic. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Elizabeth Tejada. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Nelson Salazar. Transcript, 2004; MS083.004.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Alex Pirie. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Terry Signago. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Ralph Hergert. Interview Report, 2004; MS083.004.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Community History Project. Anonymous. Interview Reports, 2004; MS083.004.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Final Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00001; Taneja, Avantika (Box 2)
    Final project report by Avantika Taneja.
    - Coming of Age in Somerville. Final Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00001.00001; Taneja, Avantika (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Draft of Final Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Andy Haydu, Transcript. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Cynthia Tchampl, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Susan Gross, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Alberto Ortiz, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Marty Martinez, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Aru Manrique, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Regina Bertholdo, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Denise Provost, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Coming of Age in Somerville. Luis "Tony" Morales, Interview Report. Avantika Taneja, 2004; MS083.004.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Notes from Focus Group. Taneja, Nicholson, van Nieuwenhuizen, 2004; MS083.004.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - La Quinceanera, 2004; MS083.004.002.00013; Arcaya, Sara (Box 2)
    Final project report by Sara Arcaya.
  - la Quinceanera, Bianca Salazar, Transcript. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Heidy P. Castro, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Jessica Tejada, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Milagro Garcia, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Daisy Maria Gomez, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Berta Guevara, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - la Quinceanera, Nelson Salazar, Interview report. Sara Arcaya, 2004; MS083.004.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville, 2004; MS083.004.002.00021; Molina, Yanelly (Box 2)
    Final project report by Yanelly Molina.
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Cesi Sosa Paterson, Transcript. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Anonymous, interview reports. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Dalie Jimenez, interview reports. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Marty Martinez, interview reports. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Fabiola Alvarez, interview reports. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Tito Meza, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Alex Pirie, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Nelson Salazar, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Mayor Jospeh Curatone, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Tony Morales, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Political Participation within the Latino Community of Somerville. Aru Mariquez, Interview report. Yanelly Molina, 2004; MS083.004.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation, 2004; MS083.004.002.00033; Goldberg, Julia; Rogers, Leah (Box 2)
    Final project report by Julia Goldberg and Leah Rogers
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Sergio Rosas, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Eva Hernandez-Morales, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Jesus Peremenendez, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Dalia Rosas, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Gene Brune, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Loretta Saint-Louis, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Donald Wood, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Jose Freitas Cabral, Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Aida Corredor, Transcript and Interview Report. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Interview Reports with Comments. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Marty Martinez, Transcript. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Medical Interpretation and Translation. Regina Bertholdo, Transcript. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues: Latinos, Related Material. Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Speaking in Tongues. Brochures Leah Rogers and Julia Goldberg., 2004; MS083.004.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - A History of Human and Civil Rights in the Somerville Latino Community, 2004; MS083.004.003.00001; Nicholson, Lindsey; Van Nieuwenhuizen, Adrienne (Box 3)
    Final project report by Lindsey Nicholson and Adrienne Van Nieuwenhuizen.
  - Religion and Community among Somerville Latinos, 2004; MS083.004.003.00002; Hickok, Spencer; Cruz, Vicente (Box 3)
    Final project report by Spencer Hickok and Vicente Cruz.
  - Rene Rosas and Teresa Ramirez, 2004-12-09; MS083.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Interview by Dalia Palchik
  - Rafael Sorto, 2004-11-11; MS083.004.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Luis A. Morales, 2004-11-11; MS083.004.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Juan Pablo Hernandez, 2004-10-27; MS083.004.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Mirag Lopez, 2004-10-25; MS083.004.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - William Fajardo, 2004-10-17; MS083.004.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Orlando Tejada, 2004-10-04; MS083.004.004.00007 (Box 4)
    Interview by Dalia Palchik and Jessica Tejada
  - Escabin and Tejada, Side A; Luis Morales, Side B, 2004-10-26 -- 2004-11-17; MS083.004.004.00008 (Box 4)
    Interview by Spencer Hickok. Escabin and Tejada recorded on October 26, 2004. Morales recorded on November 17, 2004.
  - Ralph Hergert, 2004-10-13; MS083.004.004.00009 (Box 4)
    Interview by Spencer Hickok
  - Colixto Lopez, 2004-12-07; MS083.004.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Jose Giron, 2004-10-26; MS083.004.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Daisy Gomez, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Ralph Hergert, 2004-10-15; MS083.004.004.00013 (Box 4)
    Interview by Adrienne vanNieuwenhuizen
  - Cynthia Berger and Terry Signago, 2004-10-25; MS083.004.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Alex Pirie, 2004-11-16; MS083.004.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Nelson Salazar, 2004-12-13; MS083.004.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Ives-Rose-Santdie, 2004-11-03; MS083.004.004.00017 (Box 4)
    Interview by Lindsey Nicholson and Adrienne vanNieuwenhuizen
  - Melissa McWhinney, 2004-10-20; MS083.004.004.00018 (Box 4)
    Interview by Lindsey Nicholson
  - Elizabeth Tejada, 2004-10-21; MS083.004.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Hermerejildo Moran, 2004-10-22; MS083.004.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Michael Garmen, 2004-11-04; MS083.004.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Marcos Garcia, 2004-11-08; MS083.004.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Susan Gross, 2004-10-08; MS083.004.005.00002 (Box 5)
    Interview by Avantika Taneja
  - Marty Martinez, 2004-10-27; MS083.004.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Aru Manrique, 2004-11-01; MS083.004.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Regina Bertholdo, 2004-11-03; MS083.004.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Cynthia Tschampi, 2004-11-10; MS083.004.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Denise Provost, 2004-12-10; MS083.004.005.00007 (Box 5)
    Interview by Avantika Taneja and Dalia Palchik
  - Alberto Ortiz, 2004-10-18; MS083.004.005.00008 (Box 5)
    Interview by Avantika Taneja and William Velasquez
  - Andy Haydu, 2004-11-09; MS083.004.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Berta Guevara, 2004-12-05; MS083.004.005.00010 (Box 5)
    Interview by Sara Arcaya
  - Heidy Castro, 2004-11-29; MS083.004.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Daisy Gomez, 2004-11-23; MS083.004.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Milagro Garcia, 2004-11-11; MS083.004.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Bianca Salazar, Side A; Jessica Tejada, Side B, 2004-10-15; MS083.004.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Mayor Joseph Curatone, Side A; Ismael Vasquez, Side B, 2004-12-09 -- 2004-12-17; MS083.004.005.00015 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Mayor Curatone recorded December 9, 2004. Ismael Vasquez recorded December 17, 2004.
  - Tito Meza, Side A; Alex Pirie, Side B, 2004-11-02 -- 2004-12-03; MS083.004.005.00016 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Tito Meza recorded November 2, 2004. Alex Pirie recorded December 3, 2004.
  - Dalie Jimenez, Side A; Anonymous, Side B, 2004-10-10 -- 2004-10-14; MS083.004.005.00017 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Dalie Jimenez recorded October 14, 2004. Anonymous recorded October 10, 2004.
  - Tony Morales, Side A; Aru Manriquez, Side B, 2001-12-02 -- 2004-11-22; MS083.004.005.00018 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Tony Morales recorded November 22, 2004. Aru Manriquez recorded December 2, 2004.
  - Cesi Sosa Paterson, 2004-11-16; MS083.004.005.00019 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina
  - Marty Martinez, Side A; Fabiola Alvarez, Side B, 2004-11-11 -- 2004-11-12; MS083.004.005.00020 (Box 5)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Marty Martinez recorded November 11, 2004. Fabiola Alvarez recorded November 12, 2004.
  - Cesi Sosa Paterson part II, Side A; Nelson Salazar, Side B, 2004-11-16 -- 2004-11-19; MS083.004.006.00001 (Box 6)
    Interview by Yanelly Molina. Cesi Sosa Paterson part II recorded November 16, 2004. Nelson Salazar recorded November 19, 2004.
  - Mayor Joseph Curatone, 2004-12-09; MS083.004.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Aru Manriquez Part II, 2004-12-02; MS083.004.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Loretta San-Luis, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00004 (Box 6)
    Interview by Julia S. Goldberg and Leah Rogers
  - Donald Wood, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Sergio Rosas and Eva-Hernandez Morales, 2004-10-01; MS083.004.006.00006 (Box 6)
    Interview by Julia S. Goldberg
  - Gene Brune, 2004-11-29; MS083.004.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Aida Corredor, 2004-10-22; MS083.004.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Jose Freitas Cabral, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Marty Martinez, 2004-11-14; MS083.004.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Elizabeth Tejada, 2004-11-21; MS083.004.006.00011 (Box 6)
    Interview by Leah Rogers
  - Nelson Salazar, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Alex Pirie, 2004-11-22; MS083.004.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Barbara Cassesso, 2004-10-22; MS083.004.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Marcos Pienasola, 2004-11-22; MS083.004.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Maria Terra, 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Linda Cundiff and Noreen Burke, 2004-11-18; MS083.004.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Regina Bertholdo, 2004-11-19; MS083.004.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Dr. Pieter Cohan M.D., 2004-12-03; MS083.004.006.00019 (Box 6)
- Fall 2006, MS083.005; 1.2 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials from the Fall 2006 semester.
  - Urban Borderland Fall, Administrative Data, 2006; MS083.005.024.00001 (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - Urban Borderland Fall, Administrative Data CD, 2006; MS083.005.024.00002
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somerville and the Greater Boston Area [Final Report], 2006; MS083.005.024.00003; Becker, Daniel (Box MS083 Shared 1)
    Final project report by Daniel Becker.
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area [CD files], 2006; MS083.005.024.00004; Becker, Daniel
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area [Administrative Data], 2006; MS083.005.024.00005; Becker, Daniel (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area [Release Forms], 2006; MS083.005.024.00006; Becker, Daniel (Box MS083 Shared 1)
  - The Brazilian Immigrant Experience: A study on the evolution of a Brazilian community in Somverville and the Greater Boston Area [Interview Reports], 2006; MS083.005.024.00007; Becker, Daniel (Box MS083 Shared 1)